I am ill-fated
and destined to have no sons.
I only have you two daughters.
Although I cannot
treat you both equally,
I promise
I will do my utmost to keep you safe.
As discussed,
poison Ning Yuanci on your wedding night.
I will send my men to coordinate with you,
helping you fake your death and escape.
My good daughter.
The survival
of the Xue family
is in your hands.
The auspicious hour has arrived.
Please head out now.
I just want to ask one more time
are you really the murderer
bribed by Ning Yuanci to poison me?
That is correct.
You must know...
Everyone in this world
might harm you,
except your own parents.
I have something to tell you.
You regret it.
Since I've made my decision,
I won't regret it.
But I just want to ask one thing.
What about Keying?
What about your true feelings for Keying?
I never had
any true feelings for her.
My precious daughter,
please don't be sad.
If it doesn't work out,
just find another man to love.
Will that do?
Even though their marriage
is arranged by the script,
can Xue Ruowan
really remain safe and sound?
And Ning Yuanci's injuries,
I wonder if they are serious.
What are you doing,
being so restless?
Should I go to the General's Manor
to take a look?
I just need to make sure
they are safe.
Ying'er, where are you going?
The security in this general's manor
is too lax.
Anyone can sneak in
just by pretending to be a maid.
Strange.
Why is it so quiet
on a wedding night?
I haven't seen a single person.
What happened here?
Where is your general?
Who are you?
I've never seen you before.
I...
Oh no,
there's a fire!
fire!
Which room is the bride in?
Somebody come!
I don't know.
Somebody come, hurry!
Forget it.
Put out the fire, hurry!
Hurry up.
This way.
Xue Ruowan!
Did Father send you?
What does it have to do with him?
Where is Ning Yuanci?
Why isn't he with you?
Never mind. Let's go.
I'm not leaving.
I want to wait a bit longer.
Wait for what?
To die?
Go!
Leave me alone.
Hurry up and go.
Xue Ruowan!
Stop trying to get yourself killed,
will you?
If you don't want to live, I do.
Let's go!
Did Father send you?
Great.
Help me drag her away.
Hurry.
Xue Keying!
Ning Yuanci.
As long as...
as long as you are fine.
Xue Keying!
Keying!
Somebody, help!
Get a doctor, quick!
General!
If you fail the plot missions
five times,
you will be stuck
in the script world forever.
Please get the plot back on track
as soon as possible.
Please hurry.
Do I have
to start over again
to get the plot back on track?
General,
you're finally awake.
No
way.
Where's the character bio?
Why isn't there one?
General,
what are you looking for?
Help!
I actually transmigrated into Ning Yuanci!
I'm doomed.
I only have one last chance left.
I finally got
my own body back.
General,
your wound is torn badly.
The imperial physician
told you not to move around.
How could Xue Keying
just die like this?
She was severely injured,
but she is not dead.
What did you say?
Xue
Keying!
Fortunately, the General
rescued her from the fire last night.
Thanks to the timely treatment
by the imperial physician,
her life was saved.
But for some reason,
she won't respond
no matter how we call her.
Cui Hu,
pour me a cup of water.
Yes.
The fire last night...
That means
the timeline
didn't restart the loop,
but continued.
But why did I
become Ning Yuanci,
while Xue Keying remains unconscious?
Could it be...
Ning
Yuanci!
I never had true feelings for him.
You can fool others
about your true feelings,
but you can't fool yourself.
I won't believe Xiaolan
is the one who poisoned me.
Nor would I kill someone
just to save myself.
Come on, let's drink.
A toast to you. Come on, quick.
Get out, all of you!
Why is
the General losing his temper?
Hurry.
Let's go.
General,
your wound...
Summon the imperial physician!
General, bad news!
The backyard is on fire!
The Second Lady of the Duke's Estate
seems to be here to save people too.
Sun Xiaofei,
I actually treated you
as my best friend.
Yet you stole my role
with such despicable means.
Give me my face back right now.
Let go of me.
Let go.
I'm here to save you.
The one who wants to kill you
is Ning Yuanci.
No!
Stop!
I'd like to see who dares to hit her.
Don't be afraid.
General,
you should go back to your room and rest.
I'm fine.
Your body...
By the way,
where is Xue Ruowan?
She...
Although
Xue Ruowan didn't poison
the General as instructed
by Duke Ying,
I believe
the arson and assassination
were a trap set by her
and the Duke.
What?
My father?
No.
Her father ordered her
to assassinate Ning...
assassinate me?
How come you're involved in murder
and arson too?
How many things are you hiding
from Xue Keying?
My father
told me to poison you
on our wedding day.
He said he would send someone to help me
escape.
But I didn't expect
the person he sent
was here to kill me.
This Xue Shiyan
always acts like
a loving father,
but he's actually ruthless.
He even used his own
daughter's life for power.
I agreed to marry you
because I didn't want
Xue Keying to take the risk,
pretending to turn against him.
But I didn't expect
her to come and save me again.
So Xue Ruowan's
character didn't collapse.
As expected,
there's always a reason
when the female lead turns bad.
Thank you, General, for saving my sister
and preventing me from
making a huge mistake.
From the moment
I gave you the poison,
I already knew
my fate.
Please take good care
of my sister, General.
I am at your disposal.
Disposal?
Are you in such a hurry to die?
General, please don't
be fooled by her.
We should capture her,
torture her for a confession,
and then confront Duke Ying.
We can't touch her now.
Get up.
Report!
Duke Ying brought his men
to surround the general's mansion,
demanding the general
release his daughter.
He wants to see her alive
or dead.
What?
He has the nerve to come here?